YASH KINARIWALA

Atlanta, GA

Yashkinariwalask95@gmail.com Portfolio | LinkedIn | GitHub l 678 – 697 – 8718

SUMMARY

Versatile Full Stack Developer with 2+ years of experience designing, developing, and managing complex sites and internal frameworks. Specializes in ReactJS and responsive design. Enthusiastic about approaching programming challenges from different angles and collaborating with others to create meaningful web applications.

SKILLS

- Expert in HTML/CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, ReactJS, NodeJS, Php, .NET [C#], WordPress, Shopify
- Knowledge of SQL, MongoDB, ExpressJS, Bootstrap, Handlebars, Firebase, C, C++, Git
- Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator)

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Web Developer / Designer

August 2017 - Present

Freelancer

Atlanta, GA

- Working as designer and developer to develop a custom HTML/CSS, JavaScript, MySQL and CMS based website and optimized assets for web such as Logo, Business card, Brochures with Adobe Creative Suite.
- Developing and designing various user-friendly websites for clients using the latest and optimized web standards.
- Developed complex graphics and professional designs for a variety of businesses, organizations, professionals and individuals, including custom graphic and logo design.
- Developed several websites for clients by use of CMS system a WordPress which could lead to increase in annual business profitability by 40%. See here MobileCareUSA, VioletHairSalon, SutraLounge

Technical Specialist

May 2019 - Present

LED Energy Plus

Atlanta, GA

- Currently developing quotes creating system and email sending service for current developed enterprise application. Developed enterprise grade application by technologies such as Php, MySQL, CSS, JavaScript.
- Developed a full stack web application for company's automated daily reporting tasks to increasing efficiency and allow quality assurance team to increase work speed by 70%.
- Develop, maintain, and execute comprehensive ecommerce web platform by using Shopify which increase total growth of sell by 40%. Link: GoToLedLight

Exterior Designer

August 2017 – February 2018

RV Design

Atlanta, GA

- Rendered multiple exterior elevation by using tools such as Adobe photoshop and illustrator.
- Rendered Front Elevation uses the architect's drawings.
- Developed graphic images and effects to achieve design goals.

EDUCATION

Georgia Institute of Technology

Atlanta, GA

Full Stack Web Development Program

May 2018 – November 2018

L.J INSTITUTE OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY

Ahmedabad, India

Bachelor's of Computer Application

June 2013 - May 2016